EVHEN HRECHUKHIN

• DETAILS •

Kharkiv, Ukraine 0964045840 <u>hrechukhin@gmail.com</u>

• LINKS •

Linkedin

<u>Udemy</u>

<u>Website</u>

• SKILLS •

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

SASS

Bootstrap

Gulp

Git

• LANGUAGES •

English

Russian

Ukrainian

HOBBIES

Table Tennis

PROFILE

Hi, I'm glad this resume has ended up in your hands because perhaps I am who you are looking for.

I have been doing web development for almost three years, during which time I have gained experience at all stages of product development, from planning to release. I set up servers, did front-end and back-end, and had experience in search engine optimization, but still, my strong point is the interface, which I spent more time on.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Frontend Developer at BeKey Inc., Kharkiv

August 2019 — Present

Responsible for the development of cross-browser and cross-platform sites using different CMS.

Environment: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP, Bootstrap, jQuery, Gulp, SASS, AJAX, GIT, Wordpress, Wordpress REST API, Angular, TypeScript, Webpack, Shopify, Liquid

Frontend Developer at Jose Art Gallery, Kharkiv

December 2017 — August 2019

Development dynamic, multi-browser, and SEO-compatible websites.

Environment: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, PHP, Bootstrap, jQuery, Gulp, SASS, AJAX, GIT, Wordpress, SEO;

Configuring and managing servers.

Environment: AWS, Apache, Linux, CentOS.

EDUCATION

Specialist, Kharkiv National University of Construction and Architecture, Kharkiv September 2007 — July 2013

Heat supply and exploitation of secondary heat energy resources